kmail-lists.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Klaviyo

### Our Principles

We're founded on several clear privacy principles:

  * Your trust is extremely important to us. The best learning happens where there is trust.
  * Your private information will remain confidential.
  * We will never spam you, or provide your information to others who will spam you.
  * We aim to be transparent and clear in our explanations of what we do with your data.

We understand internet privacy can be different to understand. Please don't hesitate to [reach out to us](mailto:hello@klaviyo.com) with any privacy questions or concerns.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Klaviyo collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Klaviyo's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Klaviyo's visitors use its website. From time to time, Klaviyo may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Klaviyo also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Klaviyo only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Klaviyo's websites choose to interact with Klaviyo in ways that require Klaviyo to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Klaviyo gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Klaviyo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

Part of using Klaviyo is allowing us to show you Klaviyo content on other websites. This is extremely powerful and enables learning that previously was very difficult. While you're using Klaviyo away from our website, we may record information about how you use Klaviyo and the learning materials we provide. We do not record any information about how you use other websites unrelated to Klaviyo. We also do not disclose any personally-identifying information to the websites you use Klaviyo on unless you explicitly allow us to. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Klaviyo may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Klaviyo may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Klaviyo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Klaviyo discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Klaviyo's behalf or to provide services available at Klaviyo's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Klaviyo's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Klaviyo will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Klaviyo discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Klaviyo believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Klaviyo, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Klaviyo and have supplied your email address, Klaviyo may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Klaviyo and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Klaviyo takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Klaviyo uses cookies to help Klaviyo identify and track visitors, their usage of Klaviyo website, and their website access preferences. Klaviyo visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Klaviyo's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Klaviyo's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Business Transfers

If Klaviyo, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Klaviyo goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Klaviyo may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Klaviyo may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Klaviyo's sole discretion. Klaviyo encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
